# LEO ARNOLD

# Professional JS | TS | GO | RUST | Blockchain Developer

#### **SKILLS**

Rust	Solidity	Golang
TS/JS	React/Vue	Doker
Kubernet	t Python/Django	
C/C++	Node.js	Blockchain
Web3	Angular/Ne	xy gRPC
Cosmos	WebAssemble AWS	
MySQL/MongoDB GraphQL		

#### **STRENGTHS**



.Net

#### **New Stack**

Solana

Quickly pick up new stack



#### Team management

Experience that grew and maintained team (virtual team size of roughly 10 engineers)

#### **EDUCATION**

### Degree in Engineering Management

#### Osaka University

**1** 04/2013 - 04/2016

#### FIND ME ONLINE



#### Skype

Baloo



#### Discord

Death flash#9220



### Telegram

Baloo1211

#### **INDUSTRY EXPERTISE**

#### Important expertise in the job description

#### **SUMMARY**

Highly-skilled and motivated senior JS | TS | Go | Rust developer with 8 years of experience. Enhanced performance of 30 web & blockchain applications. Increased revenue by analyzing and improving app monetization strategies. Seeking to draw on proven software development and engineering skills to build out innovative business model.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior JS | React | Rust | Solana Developer

Anedot

**1** 02/2021 - 01/2023

- Designed and programmed a load-balancing backend for handling SQL requests. Used Tokio asynchronousruntime
- Co-authored heterogeneous, asynchronous, distributed, realtime backend system coordinated with HTTP and message queues.
- Built Front-End from scratch React/Typescript with provided Figma
- Reduced the time spent on development by 53% with creating maintainable and reusable components.
- Developed Solana-Rust for lending contract which is deployed onto test net & dev net.
- Improved transaction execution environment to add functionality that enables validators to earn fees when they process transactions.
- Rewrote large majority of backend system leading to over 3 times more throught put on one third of the servers
- Reviewed & Tested deployed smart contract on Docker.

## Junior TS | GO | React | Blockchain Developer

Alamarka

**1** 02/2020 - 01/2021

- Collaborated closely with graphic designers to create beautiful, functional, and fast interfaces.
- Worked on heavy test-cases for smart contract and audit codebase.
- Introduced gRPC, Docker, Kubernetes, Golang Backend for providing endpoints real time data feeding service
- Developed P2E Gaming model NFT-staking Contract and deploy it onto Polygon network.
- Staking smart contracts with rewards token and integrated Front-End React with backend using web3.
- · Built high-performance customer facing user interface using ReactJS, Redux- saga, Hook, Tailwind CSS.

# JS | Rust | Go | Web3 Developer

Blinksale

**1** 05/2016 - 12/2019

- Currently working on building a bridge between substrate and cosmos chain using rust
- Improved transaction execution environment to add functionality that enables validators to earn fees when they process transactions.
- Demonstrated a security attack on the consensus algorithm using a testing framework.
- Implemented custom tendermint reactor, which allows a developer to write managed distributed oracle.
- Reduced the responding time on introducing eliminating unessential Web3 calls and resolving the scalability with introducing the Layer 2.
- Worked on Agile Development system and accomplished CI/CD with git actions.
- Developed Arbitrum and Optimism Layer 2 (Rolls-Up) smart contract and optimize the responding time when switching network.
- Introduced VueX for optimization and improve the performance.
- Used middleware in application to retrieve data from Back-End and to also perform RESTFUL services.
- Developed custom hashicorp vault plugins for secure private key storage, allowing non- crypto users to sign-up easily.
- Developed transfer gateway oracle to securely transfer assets between ethereum and loom network's plasmachain.